https://www.ppmsite.com/privacy/

Forums
Editing (Other Games Modding)
Forums
Editing (Other Games Modding)
Download Tiberian Sun Movies
Get Patch 2.03 (Firestorm, English)
Get TS Manual (English)
Get Patch 1.17a (Air Transport, English)
Get FinalSun (Map Editor)
Graphics Tutorials
Cameos (using PSP)
Cameos (without PSP)
Resizing Infantry in PSP
Resizing SHP with XCC
3D to SHP(TS) [RA2]
GMAX to SHP(TS)
TD Graphics to TS SHP
RA2 to TS Animations
Voxels (Mixing parts)
AI.Ini Tutorials
AI: Global View [RA2]
Tiberian Sun: Total War
Download 1.1 (FULL)
TS: Xtreme Terrain Expansion
Download CnCNet FinalSun with XTX (2020)
Graphics Tutorials
Cameos (without PSP)
Old CnC Graphics to RA2
Voxels (Mixing parts)
Task Forces
Script Types [TS]
Team Types [TS]
AI Trigger Types [TS]
Site
Download Beowulf's Rules (RA2)
Download Beowulf's Rules (YR)
ModDB Profile (RA2)
ModDB Profile (YR)
Forums
Editing (Other Games Modding)
Starting Tools
Renegade Mod Tools (Mod SDK)
Cancelled Games
Generals 2 (at CommandCOM 2013)
Starting Tools
Renegade Mod Tools (Mod SDK)
ModDB Profile
Download Final Version (0.84)
Tiberium Wars Mod SDK
WrathEd 1.07 (Unsupported 2014 Edition)
WrathEd 1.07 (Mod SDK for Kane's Wrath)
Starting Tools
WrathEd 2.0 Beta (Mod SDK)
WrathEd 1.07 (Mod SDK)
OS BIG Editor
XCC Utilities (PPM's Edition)
Resizing SHP with XCC
3D to SHP(TS) [RA2]
GMAX to SHP(TS)
Starting Tools
Art Tools (x86)
Art Tools (x64)
Art Tools Documentation
Warcraft 3
Forums
Mapping (Other Games Modding)
Get OS: Voxel Viewer 1.84
Get Voxel Builder 1.1 (Beta and Old)
XCC Utilities
Get XCC Utilities (PPM's Edition)
Search for XCC Tutorials
Terrain Tools
Get XCC TMP Editor (tomsons26lv)
Get XCC TMP Editor .05 (Metal Mario)
C&C Graphics Patcher
XCC Compatibility (TFD Patcher) (Old)
Community News Tracker
Select a topic:
PPM News Tracker
Select a topic:
Maps
Do you want to advertise at Project Perfect Mod. Find out how to do it HERE.
Privacy Policy
August 23, 2003 - 00:08
Project Perfect Mod Privacy Policy
VERSION 0.5, LAST UPDATED: MAY 29TH, 2018
In this Privacy Policy, we describe the type of data, including personal data (collectively, "data"), that we and our associated companies collect from you when you use Project Perfect Mod Websites, software and services as described in this Privacy Policy, how we use and disclose that data, and your options to access or update your data.
This Privacy Policy may be amended from time to time. The data controllers are the Project Perfect Mod Administrators. They are responsible for compliance with data protection legislation and for exercising of rights of data subjects and providing information about data processing.
About Project Perfect Mod
Project Perfect Mod (PPM) is a voluntary association that is not-for-profit. Its community strives to help the development of user created content for games. This content can be an indie game, modifications of well known games, maps for games, user creation tools, among many other kind of projects. This community does not consist of a legal entity with a physical headquarters. It is run by natural persons and its economical activities exists solely for its own survival, since server maintenance and website domains do have financial costs. Project Perfect Mod does not do any kind of profiling activity and it does not verify the accuracy of the personal data that is voluntarily provided by its registered members, except for a valid email account at the moment the visitor creates a Project Perfect Mod account.
Definitions
The following definitions are used throughout this Privacy Policy:
Project Perfect Mod Website. Any website that is the property of Project Perfect Mod, including but not limited to everything hosted under the following domains or subdomains: ppmsite.com, ppmforums.com, svn.ppmsite.com.
Project Perfect Mod Forums. Everything hosted under the ppmforums.com domain.
Project Perfect Mod Downloadable Software. Any Software Product produced by Project Perfect Mod administrators, that can be downloaded and installed on a device.
Project Perfect Mod Account. An account you create at the Project Perfect Mod Forums and which contains your email and username. It is accessed via a username and password and can be used to manage your Personal Data that you may voluntary provide. Nobody expects the Personal Data of any Project Perfect Mod Account to be accurate at all and its accuracy will not be checked by the data controller.
Project Perfect Mod Non-Registered Visitors are all visitors who browse PPM Website without being identified by a Project Perfect Mod Account. Therefore, they are not logged in on Project Perfect Mod Forums.
Project Perfect Mod Registered Visitors are all visitors who browse PPM Website being identified by a Project Perfect Mod Account. Therefore, they are logged in on Project Perfect Mod Forums.
Project Perfect Mod Terms of Use means this privacy policy.
Personal Data means any data relating to an identified or identifiable natural person. It includes email address, IP (according to the EU regulation), password and forum posts.
Why We Collect Data and What We Collect
We collect data for various reasons, such as:
a) To provide you with services and information. We may collect data which are required to provide you with the content of the Project Perfect Mod Website. Our cookies temporarily stores the IDs of the forum topics that were visited in the current session, time of the last visit and IP. For Project Perfect Mod Registered Visitors, our database may also collect the data you voluntarily provide at the moment you sign up with a new account in the forums or change your profile data, your posts and private posts in the forum, your request to be notified by replies into topics or your participation of the surveys. Some Project Perfect Mod Downloadable Software may also access our servers for checking for updates when requested by the user or in the first install, to download the required files. We may use third-party service providers, acting as data processors, to assist us in provisioning additional content to you or in our operations, such as videos from YouTube or 3D models from Sketchfab. In this case, these and any other third-party service providers may act as separate data controllers, who provide products and services complementary to our services. Further data processing performed by these service providers is governed by their privacy policies. The legal basis for this data processing is performance of contract between you and us.
b) To protect us from unlawful use of our server or services. We may collect data which are required to protect us from any unlawful, unauthorized use of our services, or which are necessary to ensure security of our services, including both data provided by you (see above) and data collected in the course of use of the Project Perfect Mod Website. We may use third-party service providers, acting as data processors, to assist us in preventing the third party software to post unauthorized advertisement on our forums, prevent the creation of PPM Accounts by bots and to prevent non-humans from downloading huge files from our servers. Currently, we are using Google ReCaptcha, which may use cookies and collect data from Project Perfect Mod Non-Registered Visitors to ensure that the visitor is a human being according to their privacy policy. The legal basis for this data processing is Project Perfect Mod's legitimate interest in protection from unlawful and insecure use of Project Perfect Mod services.
c) For internal use of analytics and statistics about the usage of Project Perfect Mod Website. We may collect data based on your use of Project Perfect Mod Website and services, and we do not associate these data with your name. We use these data to better understand usage patterns of our services and behavior of our collective audience. The legal basis for this data processing is our legitimate interest in improving our services.
Categories of data involved in data processing include:
-- usernames,
-- email address,
-- password,
-- cookies,
-- IP address,
-- whatever information displayed on user profiles and posts.
By using this site, you give us your consent to process your IP and cookies (as long as you do not block ppmsite.com or ppmforums.com cookies on your browser. You also give consent to Google and its associated companies to process your IP address and cookies for their youtube.com service, pagead2.googlesyndication.com, googleads.g.doubleclick.net, cdn3.doubleverify.com, as well as services from Google Analytics and Sketchfab. If you block these cookies on your browser, your browsing experience on Project Perfect Mod may not work correctly, since these services were not designed to run without this information. By registering a Project Perfect Mod Account, you give us your consent to process your username, email address, password and every information that you voluntarily provide to your profile until the moment you request the account to be deleted. By posting on the forums, you also give us your consent to process the posts that you create. You can manage your data and opt-outs as described in the Transparency section below.
Usage Terms of User Submitted Content
By submitting any kind of content to Project Perfect Mod Website, you must be either the original author of the content or be authorized to submit it by its creator. The responsibility of proving the authorship of the submitted content (or the consent of the original author to distribute it) is solely from the person who submits it. We may interfere if we are informed of any violations to this rule by warning or even banning the user account related to whoever submitted it and removing the violating content. All publicly submitted material might be downloaded by every visitor and modified, as long as credits are given to the original authors, unless otherwise stated by the author itself or in the license attached into it.
Children
Consistent with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent.
Transparency
To respect your privacy, before usage of your personal data, we will inform you about the categories of data we collect and the purposes we use it for. We will also inform you about the data management options that you may have. This information will be presented in Terms of Use or Privacy Policy documents at the Project Perfect Mod Website or the Project Perfect Mod Downloadable Software, if applicable. Should you wish to access and manage your data, you can do so by checking the following cookies: ppmsite.com, ppmforums.com as well as any other cookie mentioned earlier. Project Perfect Mod Registered Visitors may manage their data here, which allows the user to update and manage its personal data and also provide us with an opt-out of certain personal data collection. Visitors may also use the search feature to find all posts created by their own Project Perfect Mod Account and edit them as long as they do not constitute unlawful use of our services and that they do not violate the forum rules. If the topics of your posts are locked, you may need to request a forum moderator or administrator to edit it.
Sharing
Project Perfect Mod uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and help our advertisers better understand our audience's demographics. This is essential to keeping our service free. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process or to protect the personal safety of our users or the public.
Security
To secure your personal data, our services are designed with security and privacy in mind.
We encrypt your data in transfer and at rest where it is technically feasible. External web resources are protected by SSL encryption.
We review the processes of personal data usage before implementing them. This is done to minimize data usage and to make sure that you as the data owner is informed about the processing. When the reason for data storage expires, we remove your personal data from our servers or anonymize it for further usage. By the nature of the activity within which your data is collected, it may appear in datasets used for research. Before using the datasets for research or other purposes you are not informed of, we remove or anonymize your personal data in the datasets.
We use partners to host our services and websites and to process your data in accordance with this Privacy Policy. While choosing the partners, we ascertain their compliance with legal regulations and security standards to make sure your data are stored in a secure location with appropriate security measures in place.
Location of Your Information
The server that contain personal data are located within the EU (Frankfurt, Germany). The current data processor is Leaseweb.com, which provides a service for Revora Creative Network.
Data retention, withdrawal of approval, access to data and your rights
We may retain your data as long as we need to in order to achieve the purpose for which it was collected. We may retain your information if it is required to comply with legal obligations and/or defense in case of violation of this Privacy Policy. We may also have copies of your information in application logs, weblogs, and/or backups made for security and support purposes. These backups will not be accessible as separately delineated information. Please note, however, that you must retain a copy of all data that you have placed on our servers in the case of any loss; further, if you cease using our software and/or services, we will not be responsible for retention of any of your data.
If at any time you choose to cease using your Project Perfect Mod Account, you may ask for your data to be removed from our servers by sending a request to
or via your Project Perfect Mod Account. We may comply with it as long as your account is not banned or suspended due to misuse or unlawful use of our services. Please note, however, that you must retain a copy of all data that you have placed on our servers in the case of any loss; further, if you cease using our software and/or services, we will not be responsible for retention of any of your data.
You may manage your Personal Data in your Project Perfect Mod Account, including providing us with an opt-out for certain kinds of data collection. You are responsible for the correctness of the Personal Data you provide to us, if you really care about it.
As permitted by applicable law, EU residents may request a copy of the information that we hold about them as long as their Project Perfect Mod Account is not banned or suspended. To do so, please contact . We may take up to 30 days to comply with this request.
Moreover, as set out in locally applicable personal data protection law, if you have a non-banned and non-suspended Project Perfect Mod Account, you may have the right to: (i) request access to your personal data; (ii) request erasure of your personal data; (iii) request a restriction on the processing of your personal data; (iv) request personal data portability; or (v) object to the processing of your personal data.
-- Right of access. You may have the right to obtain from us a confirmation as to whether or not personal data concerning you are being processed, and, where that is the case, to request access to your personal data. The information about personal data processing includes the purposes of the processing, the categories of personal data concerned, and the recipients or categories of recipient to whom your personal data have been or will be disclosed, etc. However, this is not an absolute right and the interests of other individuals may restrict your right of access. Further, you may have the right to obtain a copy of your personal data undergoing processing.
-- Right to erasure (right to be forgotten). You may have the right to require us to delete your personal data as long as your Project Perfect Mod Account is not banned or suspended and  such personal data (mostly posts) do not violate the rules of the community and does not constitute of an unlawful use of our services. Note that, when your Project Perfect Mod Account gets deleted, its posts will not be deleted. They will be assigned to non-identified guests instead, for historical and research purposes. If is there any personal data that you consider to be critical, edit it or delete it before requesting us to be forgotten.
-- Right to a restriction on processing. EU users may have the right to require us to restrict the processing of your personal data under circumstances applicable by EU General Data Protection Regulation. In this case, the respective personal data will be marked and may only be processed by us for purposes that may not violate your restrictions.
-- Right to personal data portability. Under circumstances applicable by EU General Data Protection Regulation, you may have the right to receive the personal data concerning you, which you have provided to us, in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, and to transmit these personal data to another entity.
-- Right to object. Under circumstances applicable by EU General Data Protection Regulation, you may have the right to object, on grounds relating to their particular situation, at any time to the processing of your personal data by us and we can be required to no longer process your personal data.
These rights can be exercised via the email address .
You may also contact Project Perfect Mod to get up-to-date information about your personal data processing and any personal data recipients.
Changes to this Policy
This Privacy Policy is current as of the Effective Date set forth above. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please be sure to check back periodically. We will post any changes to this Privacy Policy on Project Perfect Mod Website. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affect our practices with regard to the personal information we have previously collected from you, we will endeavor to provide you with an advance notice of such change by posting a reply highlighting the change on Project Perfect Mod Forums.
Reaching out
If you have any questions or concerns, or you feel that this Privacy Policy has been violated in any way, please let us know immediately by contacting .
Posted by Banshee
Comments (18)
Login
Welcome guest.
Username:  Password: Auto Login
I forgot my password Register
Support Us
Donate to keep PPM online!
Dead Dragon Mods (Archive)
C&C Online (Generals to RA3)
CnCNet (C&C95 to Renegade)
XWIS (C&C95 to YR)
Play LotR:BfME Online
T3A: Online (LotR:BfME 1 and 2)
Project Perfect Mod Webmasters: Banshee & Sk8erkid.Website designed by Muldrake and coded by Banshee. Powered by phpBB © phpBB Group.
© 2000 - 2020
Project Perfect Mod Group. All rights reserved.
This site uses cookies. For further information, read the Privacy Policy section.
